Guide to the Department of History, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of History, Yale University, student records
1970-2017
RU 932
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
35.5
The records consist of student records of the Yale Department of History.
Yale University. Department of History
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 14-B (YRG 14-B), Records of academic departments and programs of the Yale Faculty of Arts and Sciences.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Department of History, 2003, 2009, 2013, 2014 and 2018.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically, alphabetically thereunder.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records of the Yale Department of History.
College students; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Department of History
- Graduate student records, 1970-1985; Accession 2003-A-138
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  - Graduate Student Files, Pre-1970 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Graduate Student Files, Pre-1970 (Box 8, Folder 465)
- Graduate student records for the Class of 1995, 1991-1995; Accession 2010-A-023
  Access restricted until Jan 1, 2071
- Graduate student records, 1976-2009; Accession 2014-A-046
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2084
- Graduate student records, 1985-2000; Accession 2015-A-034
  Restricted until January 1, 2075
- Graduate student records, 1997-2013; Accession 2018-A-058
  Restricted until January 1, 2089
- Graduate student records, 1994-2017; Accession 2018-A-081
  Restricted until January 1, 2093
  - Abromaitis, Bradley, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Mark, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aoto, Yoshitaka, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Armentrout, Anna, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Azarbadegan, Zeinab, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bao, Qianyi, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Baumgarten, Deborah, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Behm, Amanda, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Benoit, Alexandre, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Billiot, Shanondora, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bisceglia, Michael, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chan, Joseph, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chen, Yeshi, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chuecas, Ignacio, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Coleman, William, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Colliver, Chloe, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Craft, Jessica, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cuthbert, Robert, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Jennifer L., 2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Defroand, Alexander, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dhont, Frank, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dickens, Sarah Jones, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dimitrova, Cveta, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dinner, Deborah, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Dlamini, Jacob, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Donadon, Andrea, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Du, Hua, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Eccles, Alice, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Edel, Charles, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ehle, Philipp, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Ewen, Misha, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Fathi, Romain, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Feng, Libing, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Fenton, Miriam, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Fogg, Kevin, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Ford, Eugene, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Fujimoto, Hiroshi, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Gao, Yue, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Garcia, Mallory, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Garcia, Marcel, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Garcia, Samuel, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Gaudry, Adam, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Gilbert, Jennifer, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Gonda, Jeffrey, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Gong, Xiaolu (Annie), 2012 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Griffin, Matthew, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Griffith, Zoe, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Guarneri, Julia, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Guterres, Letitica, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Heisenberg, Lars, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Helm, Laura, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Herman, Elizabeth, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Hess, Alexandra, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Hoell, Maximilian, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Hoffman, Thomas, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Husain, Faisal, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Inguscio, Agostino, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Ivanov, Andrey, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Jakes, Susan, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Jiang, Lingnan, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Kazemi, Ranin, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Kelly, Alice, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Khan, Sulmaan, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Kinkel, Sarah, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Kleiner, Orli, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Kordick, Carmen, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Lamba, Divij, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Lee, John, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Lenoir, Charles, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Lenormand, Paul, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - LeVay, Jason, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Li, Weihua, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Ma, Xingzi, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - MacDonnell, George, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Maher, John, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Maier, Clara, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Malarney, Joseph, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Manthey, Anja, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Marquis, Paul, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - McAuliffe, Jacob, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - McNeur, Catherine, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - McShea, Bronwen, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Metcalfe, Louis, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Mitchell, Charles, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Monastryskyi, Yevhenii, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Mooney, Katherine, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Moreton, Bethany, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Morris, Robin, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Muthukumaran, Sureshkumar, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Nadzharyan, Lusine, 2014 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Nesvig, Martin, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Nielsen, Philipp, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Ptolemy, Jayne, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Putzier, Konrad, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Qugana, Hana, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Reed, Peter, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Resnikoff, Jason, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Richard, Picchi A., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rosefield, Paul, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Saeedy, Alexander, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Schlotterbeck, Marian, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Seth, Anita Malini, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sharath, Arjun, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Shaw, Ryan, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Simic, Ivan, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Annemarie, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Soares, Teodoro, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soon, Claire, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Starr, Kristie, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Tamaki, Nobuhiko, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Teo, Sze Ying, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Thomas, Courtney, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Thomas, Zoe, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Thormann, Maximillian, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Toelle, Tom, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Valbousquet, Nina, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Van Bavel, Marjolein, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Vargas, Lauren, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Venables, Mary Noll, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Wang, Adam, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Wehrman, Michael, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Willard, Miriam, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Williams, Stephen, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Wilson, David, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Wilson, Robert S., 2016 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Winder, Nathnee, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Xiong, Zi, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Yang, Mao, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 31)